(Bernadette:)Okay, Sheldon.
(Bernadette:)What happens to our neuroreceptors
when we don't get enough REM sleep?
(Sheldon:)They lose their sensitivity to serotonin
and norepinephrine.
Which leads to...?
(Sheldon:)Impaired cognitive function.
(Bernadette:)Right. So march in there,
brush your teeth and go to bed.
But I don't wanna go to bed.
I'm gonna count to three. One--
(Sheldon:)Oh, all right.
(Leonard:)That was amazing
how you handled him.
(Bernadette:)I know how to deal
with stubborn children.
(Bernadette:)My mother used to run an illegal
daycare center in our basement.
[MAN CACKLING]
Leonard. You're giggling in your sleep.
It's not me. It's my new ring tone.